creloaded.org 2014-06-25

# Loaded Commerce | Privacy Statement - Loaded Commerce

We respect your right to privacy. Any information you provide to us at this site (i.e. name, address, e-mail address and telephone number), is maintained in private files on our secure Web server and our internal systems. This information is used to enable Loaded Commerce LLC. to deliver services to you. To ensure compliance with federal law, Loaded Commerce LLC.. does not maintain information provided by children under the age of 16. 

Loaded Commerce LLC.. will only collect personally identifiable information (such as name, title, company name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address) that you voluntarily provide through our website or e-mail correspondence. We gather general navigational information about where you go on our Web site to help us improve the quality of your online shopping experience. Additional non-personally identifiable information such as domain type, browser version, service provider, and IP address may be collected to provide information regarding your use of our Web site. 

Loaded Commerce LLC.. believes in providing a safe and secure shopping experience for all of our clients. We provide stringent and effective security measures on our Web site. 

**Use of Information**

The information you supply will be used by us to fulfill your orders for our products and services, respond to your inquiries, and supply you with requested information on products and services. We may also use the information to inform you about new features, products, or services if you explicitly instruct us to do so. Loaded Commerce LLC.. at  times may provide your information to our service partners. In addition, as we continue to develop our business, we may buy or sell assets; in such transactions, user and customer information is generally one of the transferred business assets. 

We may disclose specific information about you if required by law. 

**Cookies**

Loaded Commerce LLC.. uses a browser feature known as a cookie, which assigns a unique identification to your computer. Cookies also allow Loaded Commerce LLC.. to make our sites more responsive to your needs, by delivering a better and more personalized experience to you. The cookies are typically stored on your computer’s hard drive and are used by Loaded Commerce LLC.. to track your navigation through the pages within our web site. In addition, Loaded Commerce LLC.. uses cookies to help keep track of support requests and to tell us whether you have previously visited a Loaded Commerce LLC. website. This allows registered users to avoid reentering information upon every new visit to our site. 

**User Support Forums**   
Any opinion expressed on the Loaded Commerce LLC. User Support Forums is that of its author and does not reflect the opinion of and is not endorsed by Loaded Commerce LLC.. Loaded Commerce LLC.. assumes no responsibility for the content or consequences, direct or indirect, of communications by users. 

**Links**

For your convenience, our Web site may contain links to other sites. Loaded Commerce LLC. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Changes to this Policy**

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time. Any modification will be promptly posted on this Web page. If you have questions or concerns with respect to our Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us.
